school21.net 2013-11-26

# Privacy

At School21 we know that privacy is important to our users. This Privacy Policy describes the ways in which School21 collects and shares information about you.

School21, LLC ("School21", "Company", "we", "us", "our") provides online services ("Website") to visitors to the Website ("users", "you"). By visiting the Website, whether registered or not, all users agree to Company's Terms of Service, into which this Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference. If you do not agree to the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Website.

## What Kind of Information Do We Collect about Users and Why Do We Collect It?

School21 collects information from users in order to establish and enhance our relationship to you, and to best provide Website services. When using the Website, users may be asked to provide information about themselves, including "personally identifiable" information such as your name, password, email address and mobile phone number ("Personally Identifiable Information"). In addition, through the use of Website services, users provide other information by their actions, such as time spent answering questions or viewing material, and answers to assessment questions ("Other Personal Information"). Gathering this information allows Company to provide the services on the Website in a way that is personalized to each user.

In general, Company endeavors to gather the minimal personal information about you necessary to provide the services offered on the Website.

## How Do We Collect Information?

### User-Provided Information

We receive and store information you knowingly provide to us through the Website, via computer, mobile phone, other Internet-connected device or through other means. For instance, when you register to use Website services, you may be asked to provide Personally Identifiable Information such as your name, email address, a User ID and a password. You may choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many services or features of the Website.

### Information Provided through Third Party Registrations

You may access School21 as an application on a third-party website or through a third-party solution, in which case your personal information may be transferred from the third-party in an automated fashion in order to provide a user-friendly registration experience with School21. Also, Company may provide the ability to register for Website services through third-party authentication services (such as Facebook Connect), in which case your personal information will be shared in an automated fashion with School21.

### "Automatically Collected" Information

When you use Website services, we gather Other Personal Information about your interaction with the services, such as ratings of learning objects, the correctness of answers provided to assessment questions, time spent answering assessment questions or viewing learning objects, and other information about how you are using the service. We gather this information in order to offer Website features, such as customizing the solution to meet your specific needs, and representing your progress to you and to other users you authorize to view your progress.

### Information Gathered through "Cookies"

When you visit the Website, whether or not you are registered, School21 may send cookies (small data files) to your computing device, in order to enhance your experience with the Website services. School21 may utilize both session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are destroyed when you close your browser, while persistent cookies may continue to reside on your computer. Through options you set in your browser, you may be able to remove the ability for School21 to utilize cookies on your computer. However, without cookies you may not be able to take advantage of many Website features.

### Information Gathered through Server Logs

When you use the Website, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or online service ("Server Log Data"). Server Log data may include your IP address, the address of the page you requested and other information.

### Information Gathered through Other Technical Means

If you provide your email address to School21, you may receive emails from us, and we may receive a confirmation when you open such an email, if your computer supports this type of program. Additionally, we may utilize "Clear GIFs" or other technologies to analyze traffic on the Website. We do not use Clear GIFs to collect or store Personally Identifiable Information.

## With Whom Do We Share Information?

We do not sell or rent your Personally Identifiable Information in any way.

### Public Display on Website and in Other Communications

Some of the information you provide to School21 will be displayed on the Website for other users or visitors to see.

If you register in a way that specifically authorizes another person (such as a teacher or parent) to view reports about your activity and performance on the Website (whether that registration and authorization occurred through School21's registration features or the registration features of a third-party website or service), those other persons will have access to reports detailing your activity and performance on the Website, and those other persons may be able to see your Personally Identifiable Information. In addition those other persons may receive emails, text messages, social network messages or other messages detailing your activity and performance on the Website.

School21 may display summaries of user activity on the Website, including, but not limited to, "leaderboards" listing users and their personal achievement data. These summaries may be viewable by all visitors to the Website, even viewers who have not registered with School21 and users who have no parent or teacher relationship to you. In the registration process, one piece of personally identifiable information we gather from you is your first name, which you enter into the appropriate field in the registration form ("First Name"). Because achievement summaries, such as leaderboards, most effectively encourage learning and achievement when learners can personally identify with the information displayed, the summaries may contain the First Names of users. If you do not want your First Name to be displayed in such summaries, you should not use the Website. Any person under the age of 18 must have their parents agree to Company's Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy on their behalf. If you are a parent of a child under the age of 18, and you do not want his or her First Name to be displayed, you should not permit him or her to use the Website. First Names are defined solely by users, when they enter their Personally Identifiable Information during the registration process, and Company has no control over what information users enter into the first name field during such registration process. You agree that you will only include your actual first name, and no other information (whether personally identifiable or not) in the first name field on the registration form. In addition to First Name, summaries of achievement (such as leaderboards) may display alphanumeric codes designed to help users associate a particular first name with themselves.

### Service Providers

School21's may share your personal information with service providers, agents or contractors who help us to create and provide the Website services. Those service providers may only use your personally identifiable information to provide us with specific services, and not for any other purpose.

### Aggregated Data

School21 discloses some aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data information with interested third parties to assist those third parties in understanding Website usage, viewing levels and patterns, content consumption, demographic patterns, feature effectiveness and other information about the Website.

### Business Transfer

In the event that School21, in whole or in part, is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, asset sale or change of control.

### Compliance with the Law

School21 may disclose user information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws or to respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant. We may make such disclosures without first providing notice to users.

### Protection of Company and Others

We also reserve the right to disclose user information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to: protect Company from fraudulent, unlawful or abusive uses; take precautions against liability; investigate and defend Company against any claims or allegations; assist government enforcement agencies; protect the security or integrity of the Website; and to protect the rights, property or safety of Company, our employees, our users or others.

### With Your Consent

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personally identifiable information may be shared with third parties, and you will be given the option to prevent the sharing of such information.

## What Is Our Policy Regarding Information about Children?

No person under the age of 18 is permitted to use the Website without parental permission and parental agreement to the Terms of Service on behalf of that person. We will take reasonable steps necessary to delete accounts and user information in any case where we believe a person under the age of 18 is using the Website without said parental permission and agreement.

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. School21 does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on the Website from any person under 13 years old unless Company reasonably believes that the child's parent has consented to the child's use of the Website, per the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. If Company learns that personally identifiable information of a person less than 13 years old has been collected on the Website without parental consent, then Company will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

## Is Information Secure?

### Passwords and Sign-Out

Should you register with School21, your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You can help protect against unauthorized sharing of your personal information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and by limiting access to your account by signing out each time you finish using the Website.

### Third-Party Sites

The Website may contain links to third-party websites or embedded content (such as videos) from third-party websites (collectively, "Third-Party Material), that are not owned or controlled by us. We have no knowledge about, nor do we control, the privacy policies of those third parties. In order to protect your privacy and personal information, you should investigate and understand the privacy policies of those third-parties.

### General

School21 uses certain physical, technical and managerial safeguards to protect your personal information. We cannot, however ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Company, and you do so at your own risk. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time. Company makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems, but such efforts are not a guarantee that user information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical or managerial safeguards.

## What Are My Other Choices?

You may, of course, choose not to provide personally identifiable information to School21, in which case we will not be able to provide you some or all of the features of the Website services. If you register with School21, you may have the ability to update, change or delete some of your Personally Identifiable Information, in which case we may retain previous versions of that information for our records. Should you choose to delete your account, your Other Personal Information (such as ratings or site usage data) may not be deleted.

## International Transfer

Information about you may be transferred from, and maintained on computers located outside of, your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction, to places where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide Company with information, you acknowledge and understand that we transfer personal information to the United States and process it there. By providing your personally identifiable information on the Website you consent to that transfer.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Company may periodically revise this Privacy Policy without notice to you. Such revision will be reflected by a date noted on the revised Privacy Policy. Please revisit this page to stay aware of the current Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.

## Contact Information

Please contact School21 with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, at:

School21  
PO Box11388  
Oakland, CA  94611

Last updated: January 29, 2012
